Caleb Banks, big number 88, says he's
got it.
Nowhere
get
it
Now he's going to attack it and run and
he's spun down by Dominic
runs and
not a lot
>> and 325 lb Dominique Orange able to make
the sack. This is a defense, Joe, that
only had 15 sacks coming into the year.
Big Citrus, he's just splashing vitamin
C all over.
>> Great block there on the left side by
their their stud left tackle, Tierman.
And then that's where you want to run
the football. That guy is a a NFL left
tackle.
Second and 11. Bailey picked off in
stride.
Coming back the other way, Jacobe Thomas
looked at his wrist said, "I got time
today.
Bailey, the angular quarterback, throws
another pick at the 37. Jacobe Thomas
says, "Do you remember me?
down.
Down.
with a stutter running back and Deont
Clayboard breaks a couple tackles.
Clayboard to the pylon and Winston
Sable.
Deont Claymore breaks a couple of
tackles.
Claymore
don't need to review that one.
Heat. Hey, Heat.
Heat. Heat. N.